Guide to the Division of Nutritional Sciences records,1947-2018.
Division of Nutritional Sciences records
- Series VIII. Grants and Proposals
  - Nutrition Training Grant Applications, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Nutrition Training Grant Applications, 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Nutrition Training Grant - Progress Report and DNS Seminars, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Nutrition Training Grant Application, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Training in Maternal and Child Nutrition Grant, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - UNICEF - Cornell Colloquium on Care and Nutrition of the Young Child, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - United Nations University - Scrimshaw's Proposal, 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - United Nations University - Scrimshaw's Proposal, 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - United Nations Fellowships, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - United Nations University - Intrauterine Growth Retardation Proposal, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - United Nations University, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - United Nations University's Food and Nutrition Research and Training Center - Proposal - Administered by Cornell, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - United Nations University's Food and Nutrition Research and Training Center - Proposal - Administered by Cornell, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - United Nations University's Food and Nutrition Research and Training Center - Proposal - Administered by Cornell, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - United Nations University - Proposal, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - United Nations University - Code Protocol, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - United Nations University - Scrimshaw Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - United Nations University - Scrimshaw Correspondence, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - USDA Grants, 1989-1996 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - USDA Cooperative Agreement, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - USDA Cooperative Agreement, 1995-2000 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - USDA Cooperative State Research, Education, and Extension Service Civil Rights Compliance Review, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - USDA/CSRS - Mass Spec Grant Proposal and Integration of Nutritional Goals and Food Systems, 1991, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - USDS/CSRS - Grant - Plant Foods Project, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - USDS/CSRS Grant Renewal, 1993-04 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Diagnostic Center Proposal, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Series IX. Programs
  - Brochures and Newsletters, 1988-1990 (Box 1, 25)
  - CALS - Distance Learning Initiative, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - China, 1988-1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Clinical Nutrition, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Community Nutrition - Nutrition Education, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Food and Nutrition Policy Program (CFNPP) - Annual Reports (1988-1990, 1991); Newsletter (1989); Publication Lists (1990, 1999); Africa Economic Policy Project Progress Report (1989-1990), 1988-1999 (Box 3, Folder 4A)
  - Cornell Food and Nutrition Policy Program (CFNPP) - Pew Lecture Series, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - CFNPP - Pew International Nutrition Policy, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - CFNPP - Pew Steering Committee Fellowships, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - CFNPP - Budget, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - CFNPP - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - CFNPP - Correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - CFNPP - Rockefeller Workshop, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - CFNPP - Correspondence, Memos, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - CFNPP - Correspondence, Memos, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - CFNPP - Correspondence, Memos, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - CFNPP - Correspondence, Memos, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - CFNPP - Correspondence, Memos, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - CFNPP - Advisory Committee, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - CFNPP - Africa, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - CFNPP - Bangladesh, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - CFNPP - Costa Rica Agreement, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - CFNPP - Indonesia, 1989-1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - CFNPP - Aid, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - CU Program - Explorations in the Biological Sciences, Fall 1996 - Spring 1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Dietetics Program, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Dietetics - New York Hospital Internships, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Dietetics Program, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Dietetics Program (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Dietetics Program (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Dietetics Program, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Dietetics Education Program, 1993-1999 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Dietetics Program, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Dietetics Program, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Dietetics - NY Hospital Internships, 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Dietetics - Internships, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Dietetics Loan Fund (Ruby Loper), 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Educational Collaboration in Public Health Nutrition - Cornell and John Hopkins, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - DNS: Program - Biochemistry, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program (EFNEP) - NYC and extension, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - EFNEP - 30th Anniversary Presentation, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - EFNEP, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Farmers' Market Nutrition Program Report, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Gerontology Concentration, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hispanic American Studies Program, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hispanic American Studies Program, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Hispanic American Studies Program, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hispanic American Studies Program, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Hispanic American Studies Program - Director's Search, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Institute on Aging/Gerontology Proposal, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Institute for Comparative and Environmental Toxicology, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - International Nutrition Program-brochures, memos, 1969-1994 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - International Nutrition-Annual Reports, 1970-1992 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - International Nutrition Faculty Meetings, 1982-1987, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - International Nutrition Seminars, 1984-1992 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - International Nutrition Program Graduate Questionnaire Results, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Women in International Development, 1980-1989 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Abroad Program-Questions and Answers, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - International Nutrition, 1988-1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - International Nutrition Program- Memos, Correspondence, Charter, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - International Nutrition Workshop-"Intestinal Parasites: A Priority for Primary Health Care", 1991-09 (Box 4, Folder 14A)
  - International Nutrition, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - International Agriculture Program, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Ithaca College - Applied Exercise Science Concentration, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - JSI Research - Training Institute, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - McCay Lectureship, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - McCay Lectureship, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Nutrition for Life - Grades 9 - 12, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Nutrition for Life - Grades 9 - 12, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Nutrition for Life - Grades 9 - 12, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - "Nutrition Comes Alive" - K - 6 Curriculum, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - "Nutrition Comes Alive", 1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - New York State - Department of Health (DOH) - Community Based Nutrition Monitoring, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - New York State - DOH - Community Based Nutrition Monitoring, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - New York State - DOH - Cooperative Extension Health Education - Pat Hess, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - New York State Education Programs, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - New York State Education Programs, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - New York State Joint Project with DNS, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - New York State Nutrition Surveillance Program - Elderly, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - New York State Nutrition Surveillance Program - Elderly, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - New York State Nutrition Surveillance Program - Elderly, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - New York State Nutrition Surveillance Program - Elderly, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - New York State Nutrition Surveillance Program - Elderly, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - New York State Nutrition Surveillance Program - Elderly, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - New York State Nutrition Surveillance Program - Elderly, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - New York State Nutrition Surveillance Program - Elderly, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Opportunities for Micronutrient Interventions (OMNI) - Proposal, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - University of Florence, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - University of Puerto Rico, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - CFNPP - UNICEF, 1988-1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - US Plant, Soil, and Nutrition Lab, 1989-1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - World Food Program, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Nutrition Institute, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
  - Nutrition Institute, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
  - Post-Baccalaureate Program, 2009-2010 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Dietetic Internship and Graduate Study Program, 1997-1999 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - CALS Undergraduate International Programs, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Honors Research Program, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Series X. Publications
  - "Search" - Vol. 9, no.3, 179 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Knowledge for a Healthier World, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Community and International Nutrition at Cornell University, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Brochures: Global Health, Graduate Studies, Undergraduate Studies, Nutrition Works, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Molecular and Human Nutrition at Cornell University, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Inside Information: A Guide for Graduate Studies in the DNS, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Brochures: Global Health, Graduate Studies, Undergraduate Studies, NutritionWorks, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence concerning DNS publications, videos, publicity, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Nutrition Newsletters, 1979-1980, 1981, 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Nutrition Newsletters, 1996-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Nutrition Newsletters, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Food Preservation Extension Bulletins, Before 1940 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Food Preservation Extension Bulletins, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Food Preservation Extension Bulletins, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Food Preservation Extension Bulletins, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Food Preservation Extension Bulletins, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Food Preservation Extension Bulletins, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Nutrition Activities: Preschoolers and Parents- by Jane Randell and Christine Olson, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - DNS Advising Notes, July 1996 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Department of Human Nutrition and Food Publications, Materials and Studies - Notebook (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Community Buildings Master Manual (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Bulletins - Not Dated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Food Preservation Notebook (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - "Current Knowledge on Breastfeeding"- Psiaki and Olson, 1977-12 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - "Impact of the Nutrition for Life Program on Jr. High Students in New York State"- Olson, Devine, and Frongillo, 1992-10 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - "Good for You or Bad For You: Seventh Grade Students' Perceptions of Food and Health"- Olson and Devine (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - "Dissemination of a School-Based Nutrition Education Program for Junior and Senior High School Students"- Olson, Devine, and Frongillo (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Publications List for DNS, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Profiles of the Research Faculty, Undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Brochures: DNS Facts (July 1983); Graduate Study in Nutrition (1987 and 1994); Graduate Program in Clinical Nutrition, Fellowships in Nutrition, 1988-1994 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Inside Information: A Guide to DNS, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - "History of Human Nutrition Research Programs at Cornell;" (by Daphne Roe and Mary Morrison) "Early Contributions of the 1890 Land Grant Colleges to Nutrition Research;" "Fifty Years of Nutrition Research at Cornell;" reports by Daphne Roe; History of Human Nutrition Outline, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter - Correspondence, 1989-1993 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Fact Sheet, 2013-2014 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Series XI. Reports
  - Summary of Research; Funding Profile, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report Highlights, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report to the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences (CALS) and the College of Human Ecology (CHE), 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Reports, 1974-1996 (Box 10, Folder 17-27)
  - Survey of DNS Clerical Needs and Support, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - DNS Research Associates, 1995-2008 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - DNS Lecturers, 1998-2008 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - DNS Annual Reports to College of Agriculture and Life Sciences (CALS) and College of Human Ecology (CHE), 1999-2001 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - DNS Annual Reports to CALS and CHE, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - DNS Annual Reports to CALS and CHE, 2002-2004 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - DNS Annual Reports to CALS and CHE, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - DNS Annual Reports to CALS and CHE, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - DNS Annual Reports to CHE (CD#-1958)), 1999-2005 (Box 15, Folder 24A)
  - DNS Annual Reports to CALS and CHE, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - DNS Annual Reports to CALS and CHE, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Presentations given in the Division of Nutritional Sciences, 1995-2003 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Origins of the Division of Nutritional Sciences, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Lab Survey, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - New York Farm to School News, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Annual Reports
    See additional faculty reports in electronic format in collection #23-2-2817
    - DNS Faculty Annual Reports (CD#-317-323; #1849-1850), 2001-2009 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - DNS Faculty Annual Reports (CD#-1175-1178), 2009-2012 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - DNS Faculty Annual Reports (CD#-2223-2224), 2013-2014 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Arion, William, 1984-1998 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Armbruster, Gertrude, 1954-1994 (Box 17, Folder 1A)
    - Bensadoun, Andre, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Bensadoun,Andre, 1981-2002 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
    - Bisogni, Carole, 1975-2008 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Bisogni, Carole, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Blass, Elliott, 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Bove, Caron, 2001-2003 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Brannon, Patsy, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Brannon, Patsy, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Brenna, Thomas, 1989-2008 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Brenna, Thomas, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Brink, Muriel, 1979-1980-1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 7A)
    - Campbell, Cathy, 1998-1990 (Box 14, Folder 7B)
    - Campbell, Colin, 1990, 1994-1995, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Canfield, Richard, 1990-2007 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Canfield, Richard, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Cassano, Patricia, 1988-2008 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Cassano, Patricia, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Caudill, Marie, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Caudill, Marie, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Chen, Hui, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Combs, Gerald, 1998-2001 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Devine, Carol, 1993-2008 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Devine, Carol, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Dickin, Katherine, 2003-2008 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Dollahite, Jamie, 1998-2008 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Dollahite, Jamie, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Dorosh, Paul, 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Falk, Laura, 2001-2004 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Farrell, Tracy, 1992-2004 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Frongillo, Edward, 1991-2004 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Garza, Cutberto, 1988-2003 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Gervais, Suzanne, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Gier, Emily, 2002-2008 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Gier, Emily, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Gillespie, Ardyth, 1983-1993 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Gillespie, Ardyth, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Gillespie, Ardyth, 1993-2008 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Glick, Peter, 2003-2008 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Grogan, Soneeta, 1993-2000 (Box 17, Folder 12A)
    - Gu, Zhenglong, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Gu, Zhenglong, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Haas, Jere, 1978-2008 (Box 14, Folder 24-25)
    - Haas, Jere, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Habicht, Jean-Pierre, 1985-2003 (Box 14, Folder 26-27)
    - Habicht, Jean-Pierre, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Hill, Tisa, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Islam, Sonya, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Islam, Sonya, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Kamp, Marie, 2000-2002 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Kazarinoff, Michael, 1979-1992 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Kazarinoff, Michael, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Latham, Michael C., 1983-1994, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 31-32)
    - Levistky, David A., 1986-1995, 2001-2007 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Levistky, David A., 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Lewis, Betty, 1975-2003 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Lujan, Marla, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Manor, Danny, 1999-2004 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Mapes, Martha, 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Martorell, Reynaldo, 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - McCormick, Charles, 1999-2000, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - McCormick, Charles, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - McDermid, Joann, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Nelson, Janet, 2000-2003 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Nesheim, Malden, 1976-1977,2001-2003 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Nesheim, Malden, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Noy, Noa, 1993-2002 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - O'Brien, Kimberly, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - O'Brien, Kimberly, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Olson, Christine, 1975-2008 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Olson, Christine, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Paddock, Joan Doyle, 2001-2008 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Paddock, Joan Doyle, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Parker, Robert S., 1983-2008 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Parker, Robert S., 2009 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Parra, Pilar, 1995-2003 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Parra, Pilar, 20008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Pelletier, David, 1989-2008 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Pelletier, David, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Pelto, Gretel, 2001-2004 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Pelto, Gretel, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Pinstrup-Andersen, Per, 2003-2008 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Pinstrup-Andersen, Per, 1986-1987,2009 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Qi, Ling, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Qi, Ling, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Qian, Shu-Bing, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Rasmussen, Kathleen, 1984-2008 (Box 14, Folder 51-52)
    - Rasmussen, Kathleen, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Roe, Daphne, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 52A)
    - Sahn, David, 1989-2008 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Sahn, David, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Sanjur, Diva, 1986-1987,1994-1995,1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 53A)
    - Scott-Pierce, Michelle, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Sobal, Jeffrey, 1990-2008 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Sobal, Jeffrey, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Soloway, Paul, 2003-2004, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Stark, Christina, 1983-2009 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
    - Stephenson, Lani S., 1983-1993 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Stipanuk, Martha, 1983-2009 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Stoltzfus, Rebecca, 2002-2009 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Stover, Patrick, 1994-2009 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Strawderman, Myla, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Strupp, Barbara, 1984-2003, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Swanson, Joy, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Tenney, Mary Lou, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Thonney, Patricia, 1988-2009 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Thorbecke, Erik, 1981-2003, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Travis, Susan, 1983-2009 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Utermohlen, Virginia, 2003-2009 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - West, Elise, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Wilkins, Jennifer, 1993-2009 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Wolfe, Wendy, 1993-2009 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Younger, Stephen, 2001-2009 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Annual Reports, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Human Metabolic Research Unit, 2007-2009 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Series XII. Reviews and Strategic Plans
  - Program Review, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Self-Study Volume 1 (I. Division Mission and II. Description), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Self-Study Volume 1 (III. Self-Evaluation, IV. Recommendations, & V. 1992 External Review), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Self-Study Volume 2 (Appendix A: Faculty Curricula Vitae), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6-9)
  - Self-Study Volume 3 (Appendix B: Non-Professorial Academic Curricula Vitae), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
  - Self-Study Volume 3 (Appendix C: DNS Web Page), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1999 Retreat (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - External Review - Follow-Up Report and Dean's Response, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - External Review Materials, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 7-9)
  - May 25, 2006 Faculty Retreat Notebook (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - DNS Review by USDA - Programs Report, 1981-04 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - DNS Review by USDA - Panel Report, 1981-04 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - DNS - Five Year Goals - "The Program of DNS, 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - DNS Review, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - DNS Review, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Strategic Plan, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Strategic Plan, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Strategic Plan, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Strategic Plan, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Strategic Plan, 1999-2005 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Biological Sciences Review, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - DNS Program Review, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Self-Study - Comprehensive Review, 1999-05 (Box 8, Folder 4-7)
  - DNS Planning Committee Report, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 31-32)
- Series XIII. Scholarships/Awards
  - Scholarships/Fellowships A and P and Marion Fish Cox, 1977-1978 and 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Barnes Graduate Fellowship and Memorial, 1978-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Research Funding - Bristol Myers, 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Research Funding - Bristol Myers, 1984-1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bryceson Scholarship - Jane Goodall, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bryceson Scholarship, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bryceson Scholarship - Jane Goodall, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Dana Award, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Scholarships/Fellowships - General Mills, 1971-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Scholarships/Fellowships - General Foods, 1981-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Scholarships/Fellowships - Hester; Helen Gifft; Lelchook and Hazel Hauck, 1981-1984; 1979-1980; 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Humphrey Fellows, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Humphrey Fellows, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Humphrey Fellows, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Humphrey Fellows- brochures and report "Rural Development in Third World Countries", 1993-1994; 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Quillman Fellowship, 1964-1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Quaker Oats Scholarship, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - USDA Fellowships - Grad Students, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Funding - Graduate Students, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Funding - Grants - Assistantships, 1997-2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Plaque - Jerry M. Rivers Scholarship, 1980-1999 (Box 16)
  - Plaque - Dorothy M. Proud Lectureship, 1980-1999 (Box 16)
  - Christian Berens Graduate Fellowship, 1985-2003 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Lewis and Esta Ress Fellowship, 1986-2004 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Andre Van Veen Graduate Traveling Fellowship, 1988-2003 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Charles J. Quillman Jr. Fellowship, 1990-2004 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Vincent Woo, J.P. Endowment, 1990-2004 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Paula E. Fauerbach Fellowship, 1991-2003 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Elizabeth Hester Memorial Fellowship, 1999-2001 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Grace Steininger Fellowship, 1999-2003 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Marion Fish Cox Fellowship, 1999-2004 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Richard Barnes Fellowship, 1999-2005 (Box 18, Folder 19)